power4home.com 2009-12-30

# Website Evaluation and eCommerce consultation Privacy Guarantee.

###  John Russel's Privacy Guarantee

**My Privacy Guarantee is really quite simple:  
I respect yours.**

If you need more detail than that, please read on.

I believe that clients like you deserve to be treated with the utmost respect. And that includes respecting your right to privacy. Here’s how I guarantee that.

**Data Collection and Storage**  
I’ve designed and structured my entire site so that you can visit and browse without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. The only way for me to obtain any personal information about you at all is for you to tell me yourself. 

For example, when you place an order or ask me for information, I may store your name, address and telephone number and/or email address on my secure server. Any information that is not needed immediately to process your order or request is transferred to my secure, offline database which cannot be accessed from the Internet. Your credit card number will be deleted automatically from my secure servers 31 days after you order. To comply with tax laws, I may keep a printed copy of your order on file in my Accounting Department.

**Your Email Address**  
Your email address may be automatically added to my internal database whenever you:

1\. Place an order.  
2\. Request a quote.  
3\. Subscribe to my newsletter.  
4\. Request additional information by email.

**Cookies**  
Like most online merchants, my website uses “cookies” to enhance your online shopping experience. Cookies are just little packages of data that my server sends to your computer. They cannot tell me anything about you or your computer and no other website or server except mine can access the cookies my site sends. Cookies simply allow me to track the contents of your shopping cart and personalize my site content. Without them, you’d have to write down each item you wanted to buy and then type the information into a manual form to complete your order. What a hassle! 

Thanks to cookies, ordering is quick and easy. You can browse all my product pages, just click on the items you want to add to your cart and my system will store them until you’re ready to check out. And, when you come back to shop the next time, you won’t have to re-enter your name and address info again – the cookies remember it for you, so that the checkout process is quick and convenient every time you shop. For your peace of mind though, I will ask you to re-enter your credit information every time you shop. I don’t permit my cookies to store this information. This also allows you to choose a different payment option, if you wish.

**IP Address**  
My server automatically receives and records information on my server logs from your browser including your IP Address and information about the page you have requested to view. This tells us which pages my clients are most interested in, and helps me tailor my site according to my customers’ wants and needs.

**Surveys and Questionnaires**  
From time to time, I may post an online survey or questionnaire. Your participation is completely voluntary, but greatly appreciated because these help me by providing opinions, demographic or customer satisfaction data. I use that information to enhance my customers’ online experience by tailoring my products and services according to your preferences and by offering the site content that interests you most.

**How I Use your Personal Information**  
If you have ordered from me or requested any information, I will have personal information such as your name, mailing address and/or email address on file. I may use this information for my own purposes only – to send you promotional offers, my newsletter or customer satisfaction surveys for feedback on your purchases. 

Occasionally, I may use your email address to let you know about new products, services or special offers on my site that I think would interest you. I might also email previous customers for feedback on their shopping experience. Any message I send you will always include clear, simple instructions for having your name and information permanently deleted from my lists, if you prefer. 

**Security of your Information**  
I have several security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information I control. These measures include password protection, encryption and my off-line database, which is not accessible by those on the Internet. I also conduct pre-hire criminal background checks on ALL my employees. For more information on these, and other security measures, please see my detailed Security Guarantee.

**My Information Non-Disclosure GUARANTEE**  
I will never sell, rent, give, share or otherwise disclose to any third party any information that you may provide to me about you, your business, your website or your methods and procedures, without your knowledge or consent without a subpoena or court order.

**How to Change your Information or Opt Out**  
If you wish to have me remove your personal information from my databases, simply send a blank email with “remove” in the subject line to: [ support@power4home.com](mailto:support@power4home.com?subject=Remove)[](mailto:support@power4home.com).

If you need to update the information I currently have on file (new address/email address, etc.), please send an email to:  [ support@power4home.com](mailto:support@power4home.com?subject=Update)[](mailto:update@grahamadvantage.com). 

**I Hate Spam, Too!**  
I’m committed to a strict “No Spam” policy. Whenever you receive any message from me, it will contain clear, simple instructions for having your name and information permanently removed from my lists.

Please note: For tax and legal purposes, I am not allowed to destroy paper records of orders placed with me. However, I will comply with ALL requests to remove your information from my email and print mailing lists.

**Changes to This Policy**  
I reserve the right to amend this policy as needed. But I’ll never change my Information Non-Disclosure Guarantee. If I make any substantial changes in my use of your personal information or if I am required by law to share your data, I will notify you.

**I Welcome your Questions or Suggestions**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of my site, or your dealings on this website, please feel free to contact: [ info@power4home.com](mailto:info@power4home.com?subject=Questions/Suggestions)

**Important:** This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Power4Home does not own or control. At times I my provide links or referrals to other companies. Although I am very conscientious about screening my partners carefully, I cannot be held responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites or companies which are not directly under my control.
